thegamereviews.com 2009-04-06

# The Game Reviews - Page: Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for TheGameReviews. If you have any question regarding this privacy policy, please contact us.

Information Collection and Use  
TheGameReviews is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. TheGameReviews collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. TheGameReviews uses cookies to enhance the user’s experience, often allowing a user to browse the site more quickly. The storage of such cookie is optional, and the user will still be able to use the website, with the exception of some of the site’s functions. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

Log Files and IPs  
IPs are logged in the server’s log file which is used for administering the site. Log files contain no personally identifiable information.Under very rare circumstances, log files may be furnished to 3rd party advertisers for proof of traffic information.

Sharing of Information  
We will share traffic information (number of unique visitors per day, month, user demographics) with partners and advertisers. The tracking software is completely server-based, dynamically generated, and none of this information contains personal information. Any entrants into contests run within our network may be shared with the sponsoring company of said contest.

Links  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that TheGameReviews is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Notification of Changes  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users on our homepage. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
